[{"answer": "Well, initially I was -- when I was 15 I thought I was going to go to law school and I thought that I was going to have a career at politics, most likely, I assume, behind the scenes as a staffer but then my brother, for some reason, decided that he wanted in with show business.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "Were you tempted to continue down that path and maybe not come into entertainment?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "It's hard to answer.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "How real is that, do you think?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "Well, I think we have to start to enter a phase of compromise and reconciliation because with single-digit approval ratings with the House and the Senate and all this stuff that's been going on Wall Street for the last -- you know -- you know beyond -- far beyond 10 years but now they get caught up with their hand in the cookie jar, I think things have to change.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "What do you think of the current political malaise as many people see it with Washington and almost constant deadlock battle which doesn't achieve anything for the country?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "Most definitely I am.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "Are you an Obama supporter?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "You know, my opinion on that is, I don't think that they should be forced to have health insurance but if they don't and they are penalized for that, I have no problem with it.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "And you know, I put it to her that in terms of ideology of the argument here, what is the difference really for most Americans between being made to have car insurance and being made to have health insurance?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "Would you?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "I don't know if I'm -- you know, I'm certainly not an authority and I don't know if I can answer that question responsibly but I -- the economy has shifted.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "What has gone wrong with the American business model?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "I think we have to be careful because there was a time where, you know, Paris and France were at the forefront of everything culturally and politically and then it was replaced by London and England and that was replaced by New York in America and we better watch out or it's going to be Beijing and China and we may look back 50 years from now and say in 2012 it already was Beijing and China.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "Well, it's about a gentleman who was growing up in Tehran in the '70s, came to America to be educated, went home, and throughout his education and saw openness, modernization, westernization, democracy, art, culture, freedom, popping up everywhere, glass, shiny, brand new glass buildings, universities all over the place.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "Very simply, what is this about?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "There's two phases to it.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "What has been the reaction from Iran to this book?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "It concerns me in one sense.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "Does that concern you?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "You know, it's so dense.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "What is your thoughts?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "Well, I was at the Super Bowl with my brother and after the game was over, he was at dinner, and he was looking at an e-mail and he started laughing and he showed it to me, and it's from Tina saying, is it OK for me to make an offer to your brother, actually he's my first choice.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "And what was it like?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "It was a -- it was a terrific weekend.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "A good day?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "Well, I interviewed him.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "And, you know, I am excited to see, you know, what half the stakes come down together, you know?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "Well, we'll see.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "Is that what you think?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "You know, I'm not sure.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "This relationship Alec has with the paparazzi, which seems to be deteriorating by the -- by the day, what is really that all about, do you think?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "It's hard for me to answer because I think it's all out there.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "What do you think people don't get?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "I -- he did not.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "Did he make a speech in his wedding?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "Any of the brothers (INAUDIBLE)?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "You know, it's funny.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "Because you're all like the celebrity version of the Kennedys, really, aren't you?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "The Kennedys acknowledged that like you're the entertainment version of the --", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "He did?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "Hysterical.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "Are they funny to be around?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "I accept.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "Your thoughts?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "You know, I -- I would probably avoid -- I would probably prefer that they not go into the business, but I certainly would not be disappointed if they were.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "Or given the way modern celebrity is, with all of the weird new pressures that come with it, would you prefer them to go off and be, you know, a doctor or something like that?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "Calling me Adam Baldwin.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "What's the worst thing that anyone can say to you?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "I've got to tell you, I'm not a climatologist.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "Is it?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "Well, there are folks who are going to be on the side of that we run in cycles on this planet, and because we've only been studying weather for a couple hundred years at best, and then, you know, the -- coming up with the satellite in the '60s would probably be reliable weather records.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "What is another explanation?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "Well, there's another good point there, that now we're adding super to just about everything that we have known in weather terminology.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "What is that?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "Let me first say that yes, a lot of folks would be looking forward to a great summer if it were really in summer, and it wouldn't be that unusual.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "What is the most practical, sensible advice for those people who are genuinely concerned now about the heat?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "Well, she was pleased with the interview and pleased that you appeared to be objective.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "What were her feelings?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "Well, I hope that time will do its magic in healing this wound like it does many others.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "How do you think she will now develop her case to win over public opinion?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "I can neither confirm nor deny.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "Can you confirm or deny whether that's that?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "Because I don't the answer.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "I mean, why would you not feel comfortable in confirming or denying it?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "Well, first, I have not read any of it.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "What has been her reaction?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "Well, I can only tell you that as of last night when I spoke with her, she had not seen or had any opportunity to read anything from any book.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "In relation to the specific claim that Casey herself has read these extracts, is that true and what has her reaction been to the Jose Baez book?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "It's an account.", "docId": "120703pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "And if so, why would you have had issues about her competency?", "qSentId": 549}]